HARIS LEGHARI

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Website Developer with 1+ years of experience creating and maintaining websites for clients. I am developing user-friendly, responsive websites that are optimized for both desktop and mobile devices. My expertise includes HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Python, Django, MySQL, MongoDB, and other web development technologies. I take pride in my ability to create modern, aesthetically pleasing websites that are tailored to the client's needs.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Fellowship

Institute of Emerging Careers(IEC) Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

- Learned and Implemented Web Development Tools, Environments, and Languages.
- Made 2 Capstone Projects.
- Developed the front end of websites using REACT and achieved how to develop seamless and fully responsive websites using React.

Front-end Development

Internship at Interns Pakistan Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

- An Immersive Internship Program that prepares students for the world's most in-demand career.
- A six weeks program completely based on learning and challenges.

PROJECTS

OLX REPLICA REACT APP - (ECOMMERCE WEBSITE)

Technologies used are HTML5, CSS3, and MERN Technologies.

Working Present

TODO LIST APP

MERN Technologies are

used. DEC-2022

BEST APP - WEBSITE TEMPLATE FOR COMPANY ADVERTISEMENT

Technologies used are HTML5, CSS3, and BootStrap5. OCT- 2022

CONTACT INFO



www.linkedin.com/in/harisleghari/



github.com/Harisleghari



harisleghari61@gmail.com



Sadiq Abad, Rahim Yar Khan District, Punjab, Pakistan

SKILLS

- React.js
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Python
- VS Code
- Git

- Communication
- Leadership
- Time Management
- · Problem-Solving
- Empathy

EDUCATION

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Government College University (GCU) Lahore, Pakistan

2019-2023

CERTIFICATIONS

- The Complete 2023 Web

 Development Bootcamp | Udemy
- Introduction to Artificial
 Intelligence (AI) | IBM
- Fundamentals of Network
 Communication | University of
 Colorado System